<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publication on Seohyun Kim</title>
    <link>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publication on Seohyun Kim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Examinees’ Responses to Constructed Response Items with a Supervised Topic Model</title>
      <link>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-09-13-mixslda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-09-13-mixslda/</guid>
      <description>AbstractTextual data are increasingly common in test data as many assessments include constructed response (CR) items as indicators of participants&amp;rsquo; understanding. The development of techniques based on natural language processing has made it possible for researchers to rapidly analyse large sets of textual data. One family of statistical techniques for this purpose are probabilistic topic models. Topic modelling is a technique for detecting the latent topic structure in a collection of documents and has been widely used to analyse texts in a variety of areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Association Between Body Fat and Body Mass Index from Incomplete Longitudinal Proportion Data: Findings from the Fels Study</title>
      <link>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-06-15-fels-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-06-15-fels-study/</guid>
      <description>AbstractObesity rates continue to exhibit an upward trajectory, particularly in the US, and is the underlying cause of several comorbidities, including but not limited to high blood pressure, high cholesterol, diabetes, heart disease, stroke, and cancers. To monitor obesity, body mass index (BMI) and proportion body fat (PBF) are two commonly used measurements. Although BMI and PBF changes over time in an individual’s lifespan and their relationship may also change dynamically, existing work has mostly remained cross-sectional, or separately modeling BMI and PBF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and Adolescent Outpatient Mental Health Service Utilization: an interrupted time series analysis</title>
      <link>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-06-09-covid19-interrupted-time-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-06-09-covid19-interrupted-time-series/</guid>
      <description>AbstractThe COVID-19 pandemic created challenges accessing mental health (MH) services when adolescent well-being declined. Still, little is known on how the COVID-19 pandemic affected outpatient MH service utilization for adolescents. Retrospective data was collected from electronic medical records of adolescents aged 12 to 17 years at Kaiser Permanente Mid-Atlantic States, an integrated healthcare system from January 2019 to December 2021. MH diagnoses included anxiety, mood disorder/depression, anxiety and mood disorder/depression, attention deficit/hyperactivity disorder, or psychosis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Structure and Adolescent Mental Health Service Utilization During the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-04-08-covid-19-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kim-s-h.github.io/publication/2023-04-08-covid-19-family/</guid>
      <description>AbstractPurpose: This study evaluated the relationship between sociodemographic factors including family structure and mental health service (MHS) utilization before and during the COVID-19 pandemic. We also investigated the moderation effects of the COVID-19 pandemic on MHS utilization.
Methods: Our retrospective cohort study analyzed adolescents aged 12–17 years with a mental health diagnosis as identified in the electronic medical record enrolled in Kaiser Permanente Mid-Atlantic States in Maryland and Virginia, a comprehensive integrated health system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
